Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thurs
Fri
Sat
Summer break felt much
shorter than it really was.
It's now a new term.
And yet...
Hey, could you hold up that end?
We're already busy getting ready
for our cultural festival.
You're so good with your hands, Izumi-kun.
Your feminine appeal is off the charts!
Oh... Thanks.
Whew... They can't really expect
us to do all this today, can they?
What? I think we can finish it today.
Yeah, totally!
High school girls these
days are so carefree...
You're a high school girl, too, y'know.
I'm in the costuming group,
Balloons
Ornaments
Costumes
but Shikimori-san's on decor,
so we're working separately.
Izumi Filter
Hey, you just stabbed yourself.
We need cactus, right?
Then it'd be a desert.
There's no cactus growing around here!
Looks like they're having fun...
We were in the same group last year,
so I got to talk with her a lot,
but we didn't get that chance this year.
They're so lucky...
Izumi. Get to work.
Izumi-kun, do you know how to sew this?
Oh, yeah.
You insert the needle from the back
and push it through to the front.
Wow!
He's done it again!
Oh, I get it! You're so good!
Me?! I'm the one you're mad at?!
What did I do?!
Life sure is rough for her, huh?
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#07  Cultural Festival I
Today's the first day of our
three-day cultural festival.
I'm nervous since our class's exhibit
is more demanding than last year's,
but I'll do my best!
Yuu, are you okay on time?
Oh, shoot!
Cultural Festival
Heya!
C'mon, wait up!
Cultural Festival
Welcome to
Here you go.
Thanks.
Forty-four...
DEATH
What an unlucky number.
Nothing new for me, though.
They're doing it again this year, huh?
This game is really fun, huh?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
Listen up, people!
We're gonna earn the highest
profit in the school
and win the prize that every
single student is hungry for:
the free after-party tickets!
Yeah!
Izumi, you and that costume
are tragically mismatched.
Well, no one's even gonna know who you are.
It looks hot, too.
I-Izumi-san...
Oh, Shikimori-san.
I-I don't look weird, do I?
You don't think it's too audacious?
You look super cute!
Really? You look great, too!
You two! Quit staring at each
other and get to work!
The 97th Hachiou Festival will now begin.
Tiger
Welcome! How many in your party?
Welcome!
Over here, please!
Animal Café
Class 2-4's running an animal café!
Come on down!
Hey, look. Isn't that bunny adorable?
So cute!
Wow, that's really elaborate.
Two chocolate ice creams,
one matcha ice cream,
an orange juice, a lemon squash, and...
Can I get a picture?
S-Sure!
What kind of animal are you?
Um...
What's this "giraffe parfait" like?
Excuse me! I still haven't gotten my order!
We're way too busy!
But I have to do the best I can!
Oh, crap!
What?! What did I step on?!
I don't have time to
watch where I'm walking!
Izumi-kun!
There it is! Just like always!
I...
I have to save the ice cream!
You dork.
We're all here.
Don't rush around by yourself.
Sorry.
Well, as long as you understand...
The rabbit turned the lion into a kitty-cat!
I'm exhausted.
We really had a lot of customers.
There'll probably be even more tomorrow.
Wow...
Let's walk around together
tomorrow afternoon.
Sure. I'm looking forward to it.
You'll be working in the
library all morning, right?
What'll you be doing there?
Actually...
The library's just open as a rest area,
so I won't be doing much.
I drew the three-hour shift
on the second day,
the one nobody really wanted.
Ah.
You're on duty at the animal
café all morning, right?
Yes.
What is it?
I just... feel kinda bad.
Everyone else will be working hard.
Don't worry.
I'll work hard enough for the both of us.
Shikimori-san!
I'll work my hardest at my job, too!
Just be careful not to knock
any bookshelves over, okay?
I'll work hard!
Are you listening?!
I'll work so hard!
Soba
Udon
Where do you wanna start today?
Fortunes
Destiny
Palm Reading
Love
Fortunes
Accurate
Determine
Your
Destiny
Frighteningly accurate!
200 yen per reading
Fortunes Read
Open
Come to think of it, there's supposed
to be one other person on library duty.
Library
Rest Area
Cultural Festival Venue
I hope it's someone in my grade, at least.
It'd be a little awkward to spend three
hours with someone I don't know.
Library
Notice from the Library Committee
Oh...
I wondered who would be coming.
Hi, Izumi-kun.
Kamiya-san?
You're on the library
committee again this year?
I'm glad the other person
on duty is someone I know.
Mind helping me put these books away?
Sure.
I got to know Kamiya-san through
the library committee last year.
She's the volleyball team's ace. She's tall.
She's cool and composed,
pretty, and kind to everyone.
She's someone loved and admired
by boys and girls alike.
Class 1-4
Class 2-4
Class 1-3
Class 2-1
Last year, she was in the class next to mine,
so we had library duty together.
Book Borrowing
I was really nervous at first,
but Kamiya-san was friendly
and talked to me openly.
Anyway, it's unusual for you to
draw the short straw like this.
Not really.
What's your class doing for the festival?
A café.
Really? Same as my class, then.
They must really be struggling
without you there.
Oh... Yeah, maybe.
People cried trying to stop
me from leaving yesterday.
I figured!
Café
Please don't go!
Have mercy on us!
You're always surrounded by people, huh?
You were crazy popular with the younger
students at the ball sports tournament.
Things are always chaotic
in class and at my club.
That's why I like the
occasional quiet moment.
Like... right now, for example.
Cultural Festival Venue
The library is open
as a rest area
-Library Committee
A Year and a Half Earlier
U-Um!
Would you like to borrow a book?
No, I'm here from the library committee!
I'm Izumi from Class 1-4!
Oh. Nice to meet you. I'm Kamiya.
Nice to mee— Ack!
Izumi-kun, was it?
You don't need to be so nervous.
We're in the same grade.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
It's my first time on library duty,
so I'm kinda nervous.
Thanks!
If you click this tab,
it'll sort everything for you.
This is where you input the names and
dates of everyone who borrowed books.
Got it.
You're good at explaining things, Kamiya-san.
I'm impressed.
We're starting with a run today, right?
Hi, Kamiya-san.
Hey, Izumi-kun.
You're here earlier than usual today.
Yeah.
I got the work I was asked to do for
the student council done yesterday.
My classmates asked me to
join them on a shopping run,
but I apologized and turned them down.
I see.
You're really nice, Kamiya-san.
Wh-What?
No one's ever told me that before.
Heaven, lake, flame, thunder,
wind, water, mountain, earth!
Library
Notice from the Library Committee
I see.
Then you can just relax
and leave the work to me.
Wh-What?
It's just... you seem different somehow.
Huh? In what way?
Hmm, well...
I guess...
It must be because you got a girlfriend.
Y-You know about that?
Nekozaki told me.
We're in the volleyball club together.
Her name's Shikimori-san, right?
You two are in the same class
again this year? What luck.
Anyway, she's really pretty and
an amazing person, isn't she?
She was the star of the ball
sports tournament, too.
You must be pretty proud, huh?
Kamiya-san's a lot more
talkative than usual today...
So, what was it like?
Huh?
I mean... you know...
How did you get together?
Huh?! Wh-Wh-Wh-Why do you ask that?!
I don't get to talk relationships
very often, so I was curious.
Nothing more than that.
So? What was it like?
You're super interested in this!
I swear it's not like that.
I swear there's no deeper meaning.
I-I'm just...
interested in her.
How long have you been dating?
Which one of you asked?
Wh... K-Kamiya-san...
Why is she pressing me about Shikimori-san?
Could it be that Kamiya-san...
likes Shikimori-san?!
Animal Café
Anyone in our class have matching numbers?
Couple Numbers
Hmm... Doesn't look like
there are any pairs.
Well, there are about 600 students here.
Let's go check out the other classes!
I'm totally gonna find mine this year!
Inu
Izumi
Ueda
Satou
Shikimori
Takeda
Tanachuu
Micchon, we gotta go get ready.
Glaring at the numbers isn't
gonna change anything.
You can't blame her.
This "Couple Numbers" game
jinxes the two people with the same
number to be together forever.
It was kind of a low-key hit last year, too.
Allow me to explain.
Couple Numbers is a famous
event at our school,
sponsored by the student council.
Who are you talking to?
Couple Numbers
Numbers for all 600 students in the school
are posted outside their classrooms.
The goal is to find the one student
whose number matches yours
and take a picture together to
complete this high-difficulty quest.
What "quest"?!
Well, last year, that was how Shikimori...
Couple Numbers
So it probably bugs her that some rando
might get to take a picture with Izumi.
Some rando?
I've made up my mind.
A-About what?
I will find whoever has Izumi-kun's number...
and trade with them!
Library
Rest Area
Cultural Festival Venue
Micchon, th-that face!
At least let the poor rando live!
Library
Notice from the Library Committee
So...
When did you and Shikimori-san start dating?
O-Okay, I'll tell you.
K-Kamiya-san is always so cool and calm,
but she's so interested in Shikimori-san...
Go on, tell me.
Well, we ended up walking around together
at last year's cultural festival.
Couple Numbers
What?! This is amazing, Izumi-san!
You and I have the same number!
Wow, you're right! Cool!
I wonder how often this happens...
U-Um, so, I-Izumi-san...
Would you take a pic...
This is the thing where you become
a couple after taking a picture, right?
A pic... p-picture...
I've never won a raffle before in my life!
Is a miracle like this possible?
M-Maybe...
since I was thinking of asking
Shikimori-san out today,
A p-pic... picture... w-with...
is God giving me a push?
For now, do you want to walk around?
Oh!
Where should we go?
Luck
Too bad! Your consolation
prize is a balloon!
Hey, Shikimori!
In the Clouds
Couple Numbers
Photo Booth
They're taking Couple Numbers photos.
It's in a pretty conspicuous place...
W-We'd take a photo in
the middle of all this?
Um!
Izumi-shan, would you please
take a picture with me?!
Huh?!
Oh, sorry! I was planning to
do that from the start.
D-Does that mean...
Huh?
Izumi-san?
Huh? I'm sure it was in my pocket... Huh?
Huh?! Huh?!
Izumi-san?!
I think I lost it...
It's all over.
I thought something seemed weird.
I knew this was way too lucky for me...
It was just to get my hopes up
and then let them drop.
Shikimori-san's fed up, too.
Sorry.
Maybe God's warning me not to ask her out
because I'd just cause trouble for her.
Why do I always...
Izumi-san.
What?
Let's look for your number.
We'll never find it.
How can you be so sure?
I'm positive! That's how it always is!
Then let's change that today.
Sorry!
I might not be able to find it by myself,
so would you help me look for it?!
Sure!
Let's go!
Two Hours Later
Class Play
"Those Who Gather
in the Afternoon"
In the Gym
Couple
I'm sorry! I lost my number!
But our numbers match!
You have to believe me!
Please!
They Didn't Find It
Couple Numbers
Photo Booth
The rules state that you have to take
the picture holding your numbers.
So, no.
Guess not...
Please, we beg you!
No.
Shikimori-san, we just can't—
Then let's change that today!
Couple Numbers
Photo Booth
Please!
Impossible or not...
Nothing feels worse than
not doing anything at all.
I desperately want my
picture taken with her!
Couple Numbers Photo Booth
President, what are you doing?
Hold this and stand over there.
This is great!
I'm happy for you both!
We'll take your picture over there.
I can't believe the committee
president allowed this!
Um... Thank you.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Oh, right.
And...
Good luck.
Okay, smile! He's taking it now!
I felt pathetic, but since she gave me
that push, we got our photo taken.
And after that, behind the gym...
O-One thing led to another,
and I asked her out, I guess.
Sorry to ramble like that
when you didn't even ask...
Kamiya-san?
That's the best tale of youth I've ever heard.
What an elegant reaction!
Whew... I talked about myself way too much.
I see...
I see.
There's no number 44.
There are three grades with over
fifteen classes between them.
And there's not much time left. Give it up.
It has to be someone in another class...
I wonder what the person
who has it is like...
Ozaki
Kamiya
Kanzaki
SEE YOU~